whiteflash.com 2012-10-18

# Whiteflash Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

Last updated Sept 7, 2011

Welcome, and thank you for visiting Whiteflash.com! 

For over a decade, Whiteflash Inc. (Whiteflash) has taken great pride in the relationships that it has developed with its customers and friends. We do our best to ensure that your experience with us is one that you will want to repeat and share with your friends. Your privacy is very important to us, and Whiteflash is dedicated to protecting your privacy and handling any personal information we obtain from you with care and respect.

This privacy policy is designed to answer any questions you may have about what information we collect, why we collect it, and how we use it. 

By accessing www.whiteflash.com you are agreeing to all the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy described herein. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**

When you register with Whiteflash or purchase or use products or services from Whiteflash, you provide us with information such as your name, postal address, e-mail, etc. Whiteflash considers all this information “Personally Identifiable Information”. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information like screen names or other online aliases. When other personal information (such as consumer product preferences, sizes, etc.) is directly associated with your Personally Identifiable Information, this other information is also treated like Personally Identifiable Information. When you give Whiteflash your Personally Identifiable Information, you are giving us your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information as set forth herein. We are always available to discuss your questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices. Please email us at privacy@whiteflash.com. 

**The Information We Collect**

Information You Provide To Us

In general, you can browse the Whiteflash website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. The Personally Identifiable Information we receive is provided directly by you so that Whiteflash can provide the products and services that you have requested information about, or have ordered or purchased. Typically, this information includes your name, home, billing or other physical address, e-mail address and telephone number, as well as any information associated with the foregoing. In addition, we may also collect other types of information, such as information about your purchases, gender, credit card, etc., which we may associate with Personally Identifiable Information. For example, if you purchase products or services from us, we’ll note your credit card information, the type of services or products ordered or purchased, and the date of the order or purchase. You may also provide us with photos, drawings or designs that may contain personal information. We may also collect personal information when you register with, log onto or visit the Whiteflash website or our Facebook page (such as sweepstakes, contests, games, and informational and promotional offers), and when you provide information to our customer service representatives.

Information Collected By Technology

Whiteflash also collects information through technology to improve your shopping experience with us, to make our website more interesting and useful to you, and for various purposes associated with our business. For instance, when you visit our site we collect your IP address (an IP address identifies the access point through which you enter the Internet, and is usually controlled by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your company or your college). By itself, your IP does not identify you personally. Whiteflash may use IP addresses to collect information about how often people visit various parts of our website, and we may combine IP addresses with Personally Identifiable Information if you open an account with us. 

The Whiteflash website collects information through a variety of technical methods, including cookies and Web beacons. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the site. Web beacons (also known as pixel gifs or action tags) are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of Web sites. Cookies, Web beacons and other technical methods involve the transmission of information directly to Whiteflash. Whiteflash may use the information collected through these technical methods for many purposes, including enhancing your experience on our Web site. For example, when you return to our Web site after logging in, cookies allow the site to remember who you are. Whiteflash also may use technical methods to analyze traffic patterns on our site, such as how often users visit various parts of the site, the Web site features that are most helpful to our customers, etc.

**How Whiteflash Shares Your Personally Identifiable information**

Except as set forth below, Whiteflash never lends shares or sells its customer list or the Personally Identifiable Information of its customers to third parties.

**How Your Personally Identifiable Information Is Used By Whiteflash**

Personally Identifiable Information collected under this Privacy Policy is used by Whiteflash for many purposes. For example, Whiteflash may use your personal information to send you promotional materials about goods and services (including special offers and promotions) offered by Whiteflash. You may opt out of receiving these communications at any time.

Whiteflash may also use your Personally Identifiable Information for purposes other than sending you promotional materials, which we call “Operational Uses.” For example, Whiteflash may use your information to complete transactions you requested (such as your purchase of a product or service offered by Whiteflash), or we may share your Personally Identifiable Information with credit card verification services to protect your credit card from unauthorized charges.

Finally, Whiteflash may take your Personally Identifiable Information and make it non-personally identifiable, either by combining it with information about other individuals, or by removing characteristics (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. Given the nature of this information, there are no restrictions under this Privacy Policy upon the right of Whiteflash to aggregate or de-personalize your personal information.

**Companies That Facilitate Communications and Transactions with You**

Sometimes Whiteflash hires trusted third-party service providers to perform certain services on our behalf, like a shipping company that delivers a package or a company that helps fulfill prizes for a sweepstakes. These service providers may also help with payment processing, data storage/management, webhosting, web analytics, marketing, mailing, emailing, etc. Except as separately permitted by other provisions of this Privacy Policy, these companies are allowed to gather, receive, and use your information only for the purposes described in this paragraph or to facilitate compliance with laws.

**Companies That You Previously Authorized to Obtain Your Information**

In certain circumstances, your dealings with a third party (such as PayPal) may have authorized them to obtain your Personally Identifiable Information and to use that information in accordance with the third party's own privacy practices and policies. Except as set forth herein, Whiteflash will provide such companies only the information that you authorized.

**Disclosures to Comply With Laws and Disclosures to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Whiteflash, Our Web Site and Others**

Whiteflash will disclose personal information when it believes in good faith that such disclosures (a) facilitate compliance with laws including, for example, compliance with a court order or subpoena, or (b) will help to: enforce our Terms of Use; enforce contest, sweepstakes, promotion, and/or game rules; protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of property that belongs to you; and/or, protect the safety and security of our Web site, Whiteflash, and/or third parties, including the safety and security of property that belongs to Whiteflash or third parties.

**Disclosures to Prevent Fraud Protection**

Whiteflash may, and you authorize us to, use and disclose any information, including Personally Identifiable Information: (1) that Whiteflash deems necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected fraud; (2) to other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction; and (3) to enforce any agreement we have with you.

**Sweepstakes and Other Special Events**

If you choose to participate in a special event (like a promotion or sweepstakes), Whiteflash may share your Personally Identifiable Information with those organizations participating in the applicable event, if any.

**What Kinds Of Security Measures Does Whiteflash Take To Safeguard Your Personally Identifiable Information?**

Your security and confidentiality, and the security and confidentiality of your Personally Identifiable Information are extremely important to us. Whiteflash has implemented a combination of physical and electronic security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your Personally Identifiable Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When Whiteflash transfers sensitive personal information (for example, credit card information) over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. While Whiteflash strives to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and, therefore, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us.         The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect guest information from unauthorized access and improper use. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

**Revisions To The White Flash Privacy Policy**

Whiteflash will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When a revision is made Whiteflash will revise the "last updated" date on this page. Your use of our Website constitutes your consent to this Privacy Policy, including any changes or updates.

**Referring A Friend Or Sending A Product To A Friend**

The Whiteflash Web site allows you to refer a friend or send product information to a friend. To use this service, you must provide email addresses for both you and your friend to make sure that your friend knows you have asked Whiteflash to send them an email. The information Whiteflash collects about you and your friend will be used in ways described in this Privacy Policy.

**Children Under 13**

The Whiteflash Web site is not directed toward children and we do not sell products for purchase by children. We do not knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of eighteen.

**Links**

The Whiteflash website provides links to other third-party Web sites that are not covered by this privacy policy. Whiteflash encourages you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) Web sites.

**Accessing and Updating Your Information**

If the Personally Identifiable Information that you have given to Whiteflash changes, or if you would like to access, correct, or delete such information, we will gladly provide you access to or correct or delete (to the extent allowed by law) any Personally Identifiable Information we have about you. To request access to, a correction to, or deletion of your Personally Identifiable Information, please send an e-mail to service@Whiteflash.comor contact us at 877-612-6770.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Whiteflash wants to communicate with you only if you want to continue to hear from us.

To opt out of receiving email promotions that Whiteflash sends you: (1) select "unsubscribe" on our subscription status page and enter the requested information or follow the unsubscribe instructions in any of our promotional emails; or (2) write to Customer Service at 2150 Town Square Place Suite 330, Sugar Land, TX 77479 USA .

Remember that opting out of communication with Whiteflash does not affect our communications with you via telephone or email related to your orders with us or the services you have requested from us. It also does not affect our use of your non-personally identifiable information.

**California Residents**

If you are a California resident and would like a copy of the Whiteflash notice describing what categories of personal Personally Identifiable Information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for their direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of the third parties and affiliates that received your information in the past year, please submit a written request to the following address: Whiteflash Customer Service at 2150 Town Square Place Suite 330, Sugar Land, TX 77479 USA, Attn: California Privacy. Please allow up to 30 days for us to process your request. You may submit such a request once per year.
